

Pudongxin District, Shanghai, China

🛮 (+86) 131-6701-7220 | 🗷 77qingliu@gmail.com | 🏕 www.77qingliu.com | 🖸 github.com/77QingLiu | 🛅 www.linkedin.com/in/77qingliu/

"Be the change that you want to see in the world."

Summary.

3 years experience in the pharmaceutical industry as both statistical analyst and statistical programmer. Currently working as Statistical Analyst in the Department of Statistics at Eli Lilly China Drug Development and Medical Affairs Center (LCDDMAC), supporting drug development and medical research. Received bachelor degree from Huazhong University of Science and Technology(HUST) with majoring in Public Health in 2015. Particularly interested in computer science and data science, especially data mining, data analysis, machine learning, and programming languages such as Python, R, SAS.

Work Experience _____

Eli Lilly & Company Shanghai, China

STATISTICAL ANALYST

Nov. 2016 - PRESENT

- Creating robust programs to import, analyze, interpret and report data from Clinical Trial for regulatory submissions, and manuscripts, as well
 as for communicating with key colleagues.
- · Organize and analyze data for patterns, trends and strategic insights in supporting medical research and drug development.
- Assist in selecting statistical methods for data analysis, authoring the corresponding sections of the data analysis plan, and conducting the actual analysis once a reporting database is created.
- Implement open source technology (eg. Python, R) to drive innovation and improve work efficiency, avoid tedious work and save working time.

PAREXEL International Shanghai, China

STATISTICAL PROGRAMMER

Jun. 2015 - Dov. 2016

- Building complex and reusable programs to automate the process of Data Cleaning, Validation, Analysis and Report generation.
- Production of well-formatted datasets(SDTM, ADaM) and table, listing, figures using SAS software for Phase I-IV trials and FDA submissions.

Presentation & Publication

PharmaSUG China 2017 Shanghai, China

Presenter

· Streamline Table Lookup by Embedding HASH in FCMP

Neuropsychiatric Disease and Treatment

Worldwide

Jul. 2017

AUTHOR

Jan. 2018

 Reliability and validity of the Chinese version of questionnaire—Children with Difficulties for Chinese Children or Adolescents with Attention-Deficit/Hyperactivity Disorder: a cross-sectional survey

Honors & Awards

2017 **LCDDMAC Excellence Award**, Eli Lilly & Company

Shanghai, China

2015 **Outstanding Graduate**, Huazhong University of Science and Technology

Wuhan, China

Education

HUST(Huazhong University of Science and Technology)

Wuhan, China

B.S. IN PREVENTIVE MEDICINE

Sep. 2010 - Jun. 2015

• Core Curriculum: Health Statistics, Epidemiology, Multivariate Statistics

March 25, 2018 77QINGLIU · RÉSUMÉ 1